Are we ever really going to get anywhere
near the truth?
>> Well, it's it the whole thing is just
sickening, is it not? Uh I think we all
expected more information like this. I'm
not sure any of us expected 3 million
documents all in one trunch. The real
shame of this entire episode is that for
the most part, the statute of
limitations seem to have expired and I
think it's highly unlikely that anybody
will be will be brought to justice.
Perhaps we're going to have to be happy
with just um just uh allowing these men
to to be social outcasts for the rest of
their lives. And and think of it this
way. In their obituaries, this is going
to be the story. And maybe that's worse
than uh than what we might want to see
them face right now.
>> That's right. I mean, you know, it's
it's a legacy which eclipses any
>> That's right.
>> any good doing that either of those men
may have done. and indeed all the others
who are listed including it has to be
said although there's no allegation of
of wrongdoing against for example Bill
Clinton and the current President Trump
what will happen now do you think and
you know what are the legalities around
the former prince being held to account
in front of Congress or indeed American
court
>> yeah I'm not sure that legally the
Congress can demand that he appear to uh
to testify I worked for years on Capitol
Hill and it was always more of a uh of
an informal will you do us the kindness
of appearing before the committee? They
can't subpoena him because he's not an
American citizen. He's not located in
the United States. But um really what
would it accomplish? They would ask
questions and he would either uh refuse
answer or give answers that I think most
people would find unacceptable. And so I
I don't see much uh much coming of it.
There's there's one important point that
you just raised a moment ago. A lot of
people I think thought that thought that
there would be more obvious crimes
having been committed by the likes of
Bill Clinton and Donald Trump. And we're
not seeing that right now. Both Trump
and Clinton have said that they
committed no crimes. We're seeing a lot
of AI reporting though uh saying that
that Trump did this, Trump did that, the
girl was 11, the girl was 12. None of
the none of that appears in these
documents. And so I think it's it's not
going to be any more shocking than what
it already has been.
>> Apart from being massively rich and you
know we know that Donald Trump has a
great pong for very rich men however
evil evil they are. Um apart from that
why did this man Epstein have such a
planetary gravitational pull on so many
rich famous and influential men?
>> Yeah that's really that's really the
question isn't it? Uh, in retrospect, I
I I'm not seeing it. I I don't know why
he looks creepy. His actions are creepy.
Yeah. I I can't imagine wanting to spend
more than two minutes with this with
this character, and especially when you
don't know really where his money came
from. We can speculate, but we really
don't know the actual source of his
income. Uh, he had his own island. He
had the the widest townhouse in
Manhattan worth tens of millions of
dollars. Where did this all come from?
And what was he doing with the
information that he was obviously
collecting? Why did he have every room
of that island mansion uh wired for
audio and video, including the
bathrooms? What did he intend to do with
that information? Those questions still
haven't been answered.
>> Well, you've just pointed out something
which I think is incredibly curious and
operative about this entire thing, John.
You know, the number of pictures that
were taken. I mean presumably I mean
Peter Mandlesson I've interviewed Lord
Mandlesson on a number of occasions.
He's a very canny operator. Um he would
be very aware that somebody was pointing
a lens at him as he st as he stood there
in his underpants with a young girl
looking at a laptop computer. Um as
would I'm I'm assuming although he's not
he's not got nearly the same intellect
the former Prince Andrew.
I mean, I just don't understand how
these pictures were allowed to be taken
and they seem completely, you know, at
ease with it. It's just so bizarre.
>> I I think that these were not taken by
handheld cameras. Uh, you know,
>> but it doesn't like they were done
covertly. I don't think, John,
>> no, I think they probably weren't done
Well, I maybe we have a different uh
definition of of covertly. Uh, I just
can't imagine somebody as important as
Lord Mendlesson standing in his
underpants allowing his picture to be
taken by anyone or or Bill Clinton for
that matter or Bill Gates or or anybody
else that was a regular at this uh this
island. It just seems strange to me and
it comes back to the question of why
what did he intend to do with these
photographs? What is now the liability
for the likes of Peter Mandelson and
Andrew Mountbatten Windsor? I mean, can
can they be forced to appear in front of
a an American judiciary or if if they
simply refuse to cooperate, will they
just be left to, you know, fade away
into darkness um with potential
potential guilt hanging over their
shoulders?
>> I I think the latter is the case. As I
mentioned a moment ago, the statute of
limitations on on crimes related to what
we've seen so far has expired. And so
there won't be any international arrest
warrant. There won't be a grand jury
impanled. I think that they're just
they're free to lick their wounds and
and go off into the sunset.
>> And in terms of Mr. Trump, I mean,
clearly there's a great deal going on.
He wants his legacy to be the man who,
you know, um increased America's land
mass hugely potentially with Greenland.
Good goodness knows whichever Latin
American countries he feels like um
conquering after he's you know, spent
his morning in bed watching Fox News. I
mean, is is he more or less immune to
any of this Epstein fallout? You know,
are you still talking about Jeffrey
Epstein, who he initially denied having
ever had any cognissance of what will
happen to Trump in this respect?
>> Honestly, I think nothing. The way that
the Republicans are going to spin this
is that it was Donald Trump, God bless
him, who demanded that these documents
be released, and I think that they're
just going to stick with that. Um, at
the same time, he made kind of a feeble
attempt to uh to point the finger at
Bill Clinton. The the truth is that
there are just as many pictures of
Donald Trump with Jeffrey Epste as there
are of Bill Clinton with Jeffrey Epste.
This is not a partisan issue. It's not a
political issue. Everybody's a bad guy.
Whether he has a D for Democrat after
his name or an R for Republican,
the issue is what about the women and
the girls? Where's the justice for them?
I I believe that they can still um sue
the Epstein estate, which is of course
very sizable, but for these political
figures, I think we've probably seen the
worst.
>> Let's face it, I mean, there's no
question that they're never going to
admit their admit what what they did.
There's no chance of them ever saying,
"Look, openly, we were involved in these
goings on." And remember, if they did,
if they did say that they were guilty of
some crime, why would they not be
prepared to tell us about all the other
individuals? You see, this is the
problem. If there's something very
sinister going on here and there are
certain entities that maybe are
frightened to speak like Elaine Maxwell,
she knows everything, but she's never
told anybody about the people and why
they were actually involved with
Epstein. You know, your your speaker
said they had films made of these
people. They had cameras. Well, if
they've had all these things, it's
obviously part of a blackmail scheme and
obviously as well somebody was financing
Epstein. I've heard that the KGB were
behind this. That brings to mind Putin
and it also brings to mind why Trump is
so close to Putin because he's scared of
something that maybe Putin or
>> because Donald Donald Trump is Donald
Trump is in love with rich men who
whatever their their history and it's
important I must stress you know just
because someone has appeared in these
files it doesn't mean that they're
guilty of anything necessarily.
Well, I nobody's suggesting for one
second that they are, but you say, and I
think it's a very valid argument, that
these individuals have got the
affronttery to deny everything that ever
happened.
>> There's an arrogance and the idea that
that Andrew came on with my colleague
Emily, uh, as he did, you know, so ill
advisedly, thinking he was so smart and
clever and, you know, could could bluff
his way through it, uh, was just quite
extraordinary. The naive arrogance of
the